Guide to the Student Action With Farmworkers records, 1950-2020, bulk 1992-2016 RL.01128
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- SAF Student Projects, 1986-2018; 63 boxes
  - Into the Fields: Student Documentary Work, 1990-2015 and undated
    - 2001 Folklife Documentary Project, 4 of 5 (Box 49)
      Luis Miguel Tibocha, by: Ben Campos and Jesse Gonzalez, 2001 July
    - 2001 Folklife Documentary Project, 5 of 5 (Box 49)
      Religious Traditions on Hispanic Culture, by: Natasha McDonald, 2001 July
      One Generation to the Next: Stories in Hispanic Families, by: Lorena Alvarez, Laxmi Haynes, and Bill Norton, 2001 July
      Student Action with Farmworker's 2001 Into the Fields Program, by: n/a
    - Into the Fields Documentary Project, Summer 2002, 1 of 2 (Box 49)
      Maribel Selgado, by: Gerardo Martinez, 2002 August
      Tea Time, by: Ann Plonk and Juana Ortiz, 2002 July
      Woodworker from Guanajuato, by: Andrea Waddle and Lorena Mendez, 2002 July
      Our Daily Bread, by: Alma Navarette and Raul de Anda, 2002 July
      Alacran's Apprentice, by: Nkechi Ukwu and Coby Jansen, 2002 July
      Art, Craft, and Design, by: Isabel Aguilar and Maggie Villagran, 2002 July
      Seira Reyes: An Artist's Journey, by: Samantha Fernandez and Lorena Magaña-Ortiz, 2002 August
    - Into the Fields Documentary Project, Summer 2002, 2 of 2 (Box 49)
      Reactions on Labor Camps after the Theatre Group Performs, by: Daniel Mendez, 2001 August 4
      Fourth of July, by: Manuel Rodriguez and Hope Bastian, 2002 August 5
      Evening Mass in the Fields, by: Bonnie DeBlois, 2002 July
      Por Ser Mojado, by: Alicio Carvajal, 2002 July
      Home, Sweet Home, by: Lucina Benito and Elizabeth Smith, 2002 July
      Bertha Rendón, by: Hope Bastian, 2002 August
    - Folklife Documentary Project, 2002 (Box 49)
      Genoveva Camacho's Traditional Practice of Making Herbal Medicinal Teas, by: Juana Z. Ortiz and Ann Plonk, July 2002
      Maribel Salgado, Folkloric Dancer; by: Gerardo Martinez, 2002 August 2
      Give us this day our daily bread, by: Alma Navarette and Raul de Anda, 2002 July
    - Into the Fields Folklife Documentary Project, Summer 2002, 1 of 4 (Box 49)
      Genoveva Camacho's Traditional Practice of Making Herbal Medicinal Teas, By: Juana Ortiz, 2002 July 26
      Maribel Salgado - Mexican Folkloric Dancer, by: Gerardo Martinez, 2002 Aug. 2
      Woodworking, by: Lorena Meridez
    - Into the Fields Folklife Documentary Project, Summer 2002, 2 of 4 (Box 49)
      'Give us this day our daily bread,' by: Alma Navarette and Raul de Anda
      Alacran's Apprentice, by: Coby Jansen and Nkechi Ukwu
      Art, Craft, and Design, by: Isabel Aguilar and Maggie Villagran
      Seira Reyes - An Artists Journey, by: Samantha Fernandez and Lorena Magaña-Ortiz
      Reactions on Labor Camps after the Theatre Group Performs, by: Daniel Mendez
    - Into the Fields Folklife Documentary Project, Summer 2002, 3 of 4 (Box 49)
      Evening Mass in the Fields, by: Bonnie DeBois
      Por Ser Mojado, by: Alicia Carvajal
      Home Sweet Home, by: Lucina Benito and Elizabeth Smith
    - Into the Fields Folklife Documentary Project, Summer 2002, 4 of 4 (Box 49)
      Bertha Rendon - Dueña del Restaurant Tacos Los Paisanos en Raeford, NC, by: Hope Bastian
      Slides from: Seira Reyes, Evening Mass in the Fields, 'Give us this day our daily bread,' Jose's Work, and Maribel Salgado
    - SAF Spring convening, Polaroid fun exercise, 2002 (Box 49)
    - Harnett, 2002 summer program negatives (Box 49)
    - Into the Fields Documentary Projects 2003, 1 of 2 (Box 49)
      Children's Folklore - An Introduction to Mexican Kid's Songs, by: Maureen McNamerra and Emily Hall
      Crazy Taco - 'The Taste of Mexico' in Smithfield, NC, by: Kate Vyborny and Jose Morales
      Tropical Pica Flor, by: Seema Kakad
      Narcissa Santamaria Cubias, by: Alaina Burr
    - Into the Fields Documentary Projects 2003, 2 of 2 (Box 49)
      Here come the Padrones, by: Gina Humble
      Compartir Música con la Comunidad en el Nombre de Jesus Cristo, by: Rosie Sharples and Zoe Kelly
      Piñata Making, by: Claudia Ramos and Laura Johnson
      The Body and the Blood, by: Rachel Kuck and Gricel Gamino
      Manos Curativas, by: Dora Crus and Luis Gonzalez Jr.
      Jollas Artesanales, by: Nestor Barboza
    - Into the Fields Documentary Project 2003, 1 of 5 (Box 49)
      Children's Folklore: An Introduction to Mexican Kid's Songs, by: Maureen McNamara and Emily Hall
    - Into the Fields Documentary Project 2003, 2 of 5 (Box 49)
      Crazy Taco: 'The Taste of Mexico' in Smithfield, NC, by: Kate Vyborny and Jose Morales
    - Into the Fields Documentary Project 2003, 3 of 5 (Box 49)
      Mexican Customs for Newborns and Pregnant Women, by: Amanda Grove
      Manos Curativas, by: Dora Cruz and Luis Gonzalez Jr.
    - Into the Fields Documentary Project 2003, 4 of 5 (Box 50)
      Here Come the Padrones, by: Gina Humble
    - Into the Fields Documentary Project 2003, 5 of 5 (Box 50)
    - SAF Symposium Action at Publix, 2003, by: Stephanie Etaine (Box 50)
    - SAF Symposium Action at Publix, 2003, by: Stephanie Etaine, slides (Box 50)
    - Immigrant Workers Freedom Ride, Durham, NC, 2003 Sep. 30, by: Laura Drey (Box 50)
    - Into the Fields Documentary Projects, 2004, 1 of 4 (Box 50)
      De Punto a Puntado, by: Maria Negrete, 2004 July
      Mi Sufrimiento, by: Michael Hachey and Miguel A. Blancas
    - Into the Fields Documentary Projects, 2004, 2 of 4 (Box 50)
      Healthy Cooking with Don Pablo, by: Elida Molina and Margaret Rife, 2004 July
      Pencil Drawing, By: Maria Cristina Gómez, 2004 June
      Music of Life, by: Alejandra Pérez and Remy Martinez, 2004 August
    - Into the Fields Documentary Projects, 2004, 3 of 4 (Box 50)
      An Instrument of God, by: Natalie Lamela and Lyndsey Beutin, 2004 June
      Pedro Hernandez, by: Serene Myers and Joseph Lee, 2004 August
    - Into the Fields Documentary Projects, 2004, 4 of 4 (Box 50)
      El Dia de la Cruz, by: Gabriela Rodriguez and Amanda Marshalls, 2004 July
      Passing the Time, Wire Scorpions and Volleyball in Henry Chancy Camp, by: Ann Warshaw and Carla Martinez
      Celebrations, by: Jessica Ramirez and Marya Millard, 2004 June-July
    - 2004 Celebrations, by Jessica Ramirez and Manja Millard, 2 folders (Box 50)
    - Into the Fields Folklife Documentary Projects, 2005, 1 of 3 (Box 50)
      Musical Talents by Fernando Camacho 'Musical Passion,' by: Guillermo Raya and Regnaldo Sosa
      Por la Vida que Nos a Brindado, by: Rocio Rangel and Noah Robert Raper
      Melchor Tomas - Life, Struggle, and Tradition of Latino Farmers, by: Morgan Gregson and Walter Ramirez
      Raíces Aztecas, by: Guadalupe Huitron, Jesus Escobar
    - Into the Fields Folklife Documentary Projects, 2005, 2 of 3 (Box 50)
      Untitled, by: Ana Gayton
      In the Kitchen with Mauro, by: Jaime Duggan
      Carrying the Taste of the Past into the Future, by: Joslyn Wiley and Alicia Marquez
      Passion for a Net, by: Jose de Jesus Franco and Maria Singleton
      Hablando y Alabando, by: Nakashia Dunner
    - Into the Fields Folklife Documentary Projects, 2005, 3 of 3 (Box 50)
      America Pavon - Cruzando la Frontera, by: Lupita Lopez and Julia Finkelstein
      Una Tradicíon que Cambia, by: Laura Bartels and Adelina Fuente
      El Guerro y la Hormiga, by: Ramon Zepeda and Nereida Arguijo
    - 2005 ITF Documentary Project, by: Carmela Meehan (Box 50)
    - SAF/CDs Our Stories/Our Dreams Documentary Project 2006, 1 of 12 (Box 50)
      Working as a Family: Foundations of Educational Achievements and Aspirations, Farmworkers in North Carolina, by: Tom Allin and Kelley Haven, 2006 Dec. 14
      When the Leaves Begin to Fall, A Struggle for Education and the Better Life, by: Erik Anderson, Deon McCormick, 2006
      Mientras las Hojas Sigan Cayendo, by: Isabel G.N., 2004-2005
    - SAF/CDs Our Stories/Our Dreams Documentary Project 2006, 2 of 12 (Box 50)
      Nada Mas, A Farmworker's Story of Family, Religion, and Work, by: Carina Barnett-Loro and Macey Stapleton, 2006, December 14
    - SAF/CDs Our Stories/Our Dreams Documentary Project 2006, 3 of 12 (Box 50)
      Volunteering at the Proyecto de Trabajadores Agrícolas, by: Avery Resor, 2006
    - SAF/CDs Our Stories/Our Dreams Documentary Project 2006, 4 of 12 (Box 50)
      I know how they're suffering in the fields, Leonardo Galvin's Journey from Farmworker to Advocate, by: Avery Resor and Paul Kliest, Jr., 2006 Dec. 14
    - SAF/CDs Our Stories/Our Dreams Documentary Project 2006, 5 of 12 (Box 50)
      To Laugh and Cry at the Same Time, Veronica Alvarez-Coyt, by: Rebecca Fairchild, 2006 Dec. 14
      Working for Change, by: Youngjoo Ha and Glenn Love, 2006
    - SAF/CDs Our Stories/Our Dreams Documentary Project 2006, 6 of 12 (Box 50)
    - SAF/CDs Our Stories/Our Dreams Documentary Project 2006, 7 of 12 (Box 50)
      Dos Mundos, by: Miguel Perez; Title: Decisions Along the Way, by: Natashia Vasquez and Sarah Stephens
      Educational Aspirations, by: Jannah Tudiver
    - SAF/CDs Our Stories/Our Dreams Documentary Project 2006, 8 of 12 (Box 50)
      Educational Aspirations, by: Jannah Tudiver (CDs contain sensitive material)
    - SAF/CDs Our Stories/Our Dreams Documentary Project 2006, 9 of 12 (Box 50)
      Through the eyes of a tobacco worker, by: Luis Arreguin
      Rapture in the Fields, by: Erica Bondy, Aylwin Lo and Leonila Rivera
      Everyday Superman, by: Jessamyn Bowling and Amy Gellatly
    - SAF/CDs Our Stories/Our Dreams Documentary Project 2006, 10 of 12 (Box 50)
    - SAF/CDs Our Stories/Our Dreams Documentary Project 2006, 11 of 12 (Box 50)
      The Ever-Retreating Horizon of Equality, by: Dan Dwyer and Erica Bratz, 2006 August 8
    - SAF/CDs Our Stories/Our Dreams Documentary Project 2006, 12 of 12 (Box 50)
      Vida fuera del Campo, by: Jerrina Rodriguez and Jessica Calderon
      Ver por Adelante, by: Sanjuana Garcia and Mary Lohman
      Una Familia Guatemalteca, by: Benjamin Gaspar
    - CDS 2006 Intern Sara Scott (Archive Materials), 1 of 1 (Box 50)
    - 2006 Doc Intern Bart Evans, 1 of 1 (Box 50)
      Voices from the Fields, by: Bart Evans, 2006
      Release forms for Amelia Alexander, 2007 July
    - Documentary Projects, 2006-2007, 1 of 7 (Box 51)
      Through the eyes of a tobacco worker, by: Luis Arreguin, 2006
      Dos Mundos, by: Miguel Perez, 2006
      Educational Aspirations, by: Jessica Calderon and Jerrina Rodriguez, 2006
      Rapture in the Fields, by: Erica Bondy, Aylwin Lo and Leonila Rivera, 2006
      El Dúo Dinámico, by: Luisa Baeza and Yesica Orozco, 2007
      One of Many Success Stories, Juan Frias past and present, by: Heriberto Martinez, 2007
      Educational Aspirations, by: Deborah Cramer, 2007
    - Documentary Projects, 2006-2007, 2 of 7 (Box 51)
      Una mujer realizada, by: Kendal Walters, 2007
      Me toco mucho suerte... Eleuterio el Oportunista, by: Maria Banuelos and Alice Wheet, 2007
      Everyday Superman, by: Jessamyn Bowling and Amy Gellatly, 2006
      Ver por Adelante, by: SanJuana Garcia and Mary Lohman, 2006
    - Documentary Projects, 2006-2007, 3 of 7 (Box 51)
      A Taste of Mexico, by: Deborah Cramer, 2007
      Learning from Each Other, by: Liza Hayes-Lozado and Adriana Sanchez, 2007
      El trabajador de Tyson (The worker at Tyson), by: Jonathan Luna, 2007
    - Documentary Projects, 2006-2007, 4 of 7 (Box 51)
      The Pursuit of Success and Happiness, by: Meghan Antol and Oscar Vasquez, 2007
      Dos Vidas, Un Sueno (Two Lives, One Dream), by: Elizabeth Arias and Elizabeth Tomas, 2007
    - Documentary Projects, 2006-2007, 5 of 7 (Box 51)
      El Dúo Dinámico (The Dynamic Duo), by: Luisa Baeza and Yesica Orozco, 2007
      Me toco mucha suerte: Eleuterio el oportunista (I was touched by lots of luck: Eleuterio the opportunist), by: Maria Banuelos and Alice Wheet, 2007
    - Documentary Projects, 2006-2007, 6 of 7 (Box 51)
      Servidora de Dios (Servant of God), by: Maribel Maldonado and Charolette Sibley, 2007
      One of Many Success Stories: Juan Frias, by: Heriberto Martinez, 2007
    - Documentary Projects, 2006-2007, 7 of 7 (Box 51)
      Christmas Tree Family, by: Claire McLendon, 2007
      Una mujer realizada (A fully realized/complete woman), by: Kendal Walters, 2007
    - Alix Blair Project Materials, Summer 2007, 1 of 1 (Box 51)
    - Folklife Documentary Project, 2007, 1 of 2 (Box 51)
      Mystery Man Documentary, by: Maria Cristina Herrera, 2007 July
      Hidden Heroes of Farmworker Justice Movement, by: Jorja Cummings, 2007 July-August
      Rural and Migrant Ministry, by: Leah Russell, 2007 August 9
    - Folklife Documentary Project, 2007, 2 of 2 (Box 51)
      Title: The Sights of the Shore, by: Walker Somerville, 2007 August
    - Folklife Documentary Project, 2008, 1 of 1 (Box 51)
      Cristina, by: Rachel craft, Rachel McGill, and Pablo Buenrostro, 2008 Summer
      La Víbora en La Campana; by: Stephanie Gans, 2008 August
      Making Ripples, A Rope to Climb, by: Leanne Tory-Murphy, 2008 August
      Constructing a Future, Community Empowerment Through Education and Health, by: Pablo Buenrostro, Rachel Craft, Rachel McGill, 2008 Summer
      Educational Aspirations, by: Rebecca Crain, 2008 July
    - Documentary Project, 2008, 1 of 7 (Box 51)
      Quién Hablará por Ellos? Crónicas de un Trabajador Agrícola, by: Mariela Cedeño, 2008 January 8
      Mi vida es una prisión, mi corazón una canción, by: Amy Petrocy, 2008 August 8
      interview with Victor Mendoza, by: Amy Petrocy, 2008 June 29
    - Documentary Project, 2008, 2 of 7 (Box 51)
      Victor Mendoza's work (writings and drawings), by: Amy Petrocy, 2008 June 30
    - Documentary Project, 2008, 3 of 7 (Box 51)
      Don Juan Camacho, by: Jose David Lopez and George Lozano
    - Documentary Project, 2008, 4 of 7 (Box 51)
      Untitled, by: Leticia Perez, Reed Weatherill, and Tarynness (sic), 2008 August 8
    - Documentary Project, 2008, 5 of 7 (Box 51)
      The Giving Tree, by: Jackie Fitzgerald, 2008 August 6
      Patricio Bros - Unfinished Business, by: Jackie Fitzgerald, 2008 summer
    - Documentary Project, 2008, 6 of 7 (Box 51)
      Coincidental Encounter - Realistic meaning/cliché understanding, by: Yazmin Garcia Rico, 2008 August 3
    - Documentary Project, 2008, 7 of 7 (Box 51)
      Dreams Broken, Offers Rebuilt(?) - A Story of Juan Frias, by: Michael Ives Taylor, 2008 August 9
      Well, besides the pay, I like helping people, by: Barbie Spitz, 2008 August 8
      Farmworker's Wife, by: Hilario Chavez, Salvador Cordoso, 2008 August 9
    - Documentary, 2009, 2 folders (Box 99)
    - Documentary Award, 2008-2009 (Box 99)
    - Documentary Award, 2010 (Box 99)
    - Documentary, by: Dayanna Diaz, Jennifer Gonzalez and April Simon, 2009, CD separated to Box 105 (Box 99)
    - Documentary, by: Maria Mondujano and Jazmin Posas, 2009 (Box 99)
      CD moved to Box 105.
    - Documentary work, 2009, 2 folders (Box 100)
      Media discs moved to Box 105.
    - Documentary Projects, 2010; 13 folders
      Originally housed in three binders enclosing thirteen projects that include paper narratives, paper records, some photographs, and audiovisual media. Projects have been foldered individually and are listed as item-level entries below.
      Audiovisual media have been separated and migrated to a library server. These typically include oral histories and photographic images. Digital files are available on request.
      - Documentary, 2010 (Box 99)
      - Breaking the Silence, by: Escobar, Pedro and Pounds, Benjamin, 2010; 66 files; approximately 250 megabytes. (Box 113, Digital-materials RL01128-SET-0021, Optical-disc RL01128-OP-0004)
        Includes still image files in JPEG format, document files in MS Word format, and moving image files in AVI format.
      - Gracias a Dios, by: Rivera, Irene and Chavez, Natividad, 2010; 205 files; approximately 225 megabytes. (Box 113, Digital-materials RL01128-SET-0021, Optical-disc RL01128-OP-0005)
      - The Story of a Migrant U.S. Citizen, by: Lamas, Eva and Suarez, Jelissa, 2010; 36 files; approximately 50 megabytes. (Box 113, Digital-materials RL01128-SET-0021, Optical-disc RL01128-OP-0007)
        Includes still image files in JPEG format and document files in MS Word format.
      - Untitled, by: Moore, Elizabeth and El-Sourady, Dida, 2010; 21 files; approximamtely 50 megabytes. (Box 113, Digital-materials RL01128-SET-0021, Optical-disc RL01128-OP-0006)
        Includes still image files in JPEG format.
      - Marisol y familia, by: Hernandez, Brenda and Vonk, Levi, 2010; 253 files; approximately 575 megabytes. (Box 113, Digital-materials RL01128-SET-0021, Optical-disc RL01128-OP-0008, RL01128-OP-0009)
        Includes still image files in JPEG format and video files in Apple Quicktime format.
      - El Pinero, by Webster, Charles, 2010; Approximately 1400 files; approximately 600 megabytes. (Box 113, Digital-materials RL01128-SET-0021, Optical-disc RL01128-OP-0010, RL01128-OP-0016)
        Includes still image files in JPEG format, document files in MS Word and HTML formats, audio files in MP3 format, and multimedia files in Adobe Flash format.
      - Labor Lore, by: Sanchez, Adriana and Cardenas, Denisse, 2010; 35 files; approximately 25 megabytes. (Box 113, Digital-materials RL01128-SET-0021, Optical-disc RL01128-OP-0011)
        Includes still image files in JPEG format and document files in MS Word and Powerpoint formats.
      - Live Today and Fight Tomorrow, by: Granados, Lucia and Sosa, Alvaro, 2010; Approximately 550 files; 400 megabytes. (Box 113, Digital-materials RL01128-SET-0021, Optical-disc RL01128-OP-0012, RL01128-OP-0017)
        Includes still image files (PNG, JPEG, SVG, and BMP formats), web files (HTML and CSS formats), document files in MS Word format, and audio viles in WAV and WMV formats.
      - Suenos en los Campos, by: Lozano Villegas, Michelle and Erlandson, Kirby, 2010; Approximately 125 files; 75 megabytes. (Box 113, Digital-materials RL01128-SET-0021, Optical-disc RL01128-OP-0013, RL01128-OP-0014)
      - Necesidad-Necessity, by: Ross, Amanda, 2010; Approximately 900 files; 800 megabytes. (Box 113, Digital-materials RL01128-SET-0021, Optical-disc RL01128-OP-0018, RL01128-OP-0019)
        Includes still image files in JPEG format, document files in MS Word and XML formats, audio files in MP3 format, and multimedia files in Adobe Flash format.
      - Adelante, by: El-Sourady, Dida, 2010; 285 files; approximately 100 megabytes. (Box 113, Digital-materials RL01128-SET-0021, Optical-disc RL01128-OP-0020)
        Includes still image files in JPEG format, document files in XML format, audio files in MP3 format, and multimedia files in Adobe Flash format.
      - Untitled, by: Mallando, Angelita and Gibbs, Devin, 2010; Approximately 225 files; 1 gigabyte. (Box 113, Digital-materials RL01128-SET-0021, Optical-disc RL01128-OP-0021, RL01128-OP-0022)
        Includes still image files in JPEG format, audio files in WAV and MP3 formats, and document files in MS Word format
    - Documentary Projects, 2011
      Originally housed in one binder with twelve projects. Projects have been foldered individually and are listed below.
      - Documentary, 2011 (Box 99)
      - Felix, by: Borja, Maria Emilia and Moorefield, Bryan, 2011; 30 files; approximately 1 gigabyte. (Box 113, Digital-materials RL01128-SET-0021, Optical-disc RL01128-OP-0023 - RL01128-OP-0025)
        Includes video files in MP4 format, still image files in JPEG format, document files in MS Word format, and audio files in MP3 format.
      - En Busca de Una Salida, by: Huebner, Dashiell and Garcia-Ruiz, Octavio, 2011; 81 files; approximately 100 megabytes. (Box 113, Digital-materials RL01128-SET-0021, Optical-disc RL01128-OP-0026)
        Includes still images in JPEG format, document files in MS Word format, and audio files in WAV format.
      - Lo que siembras, los echas, by: Leon, Yesenia and Cruz, Beatriz, 2011; 233 files; approximately 50 megabytes. (Box 113, Digital-materials RL01128-SET-0021, Optical-disc RL01128-OP-0027)
        Includes still image files in JPEG format and document files in PDF and MS Word formats.
      - Una Pequena Chronica del Trabajo de Don Abelardo, by: Hinek, Cecelia and Ferreyra, Guadalupe, 2011; 160 files; approximately 2 gigabytes. (Box 113, Digital-materials RL01128-SET-0021, Optical-disc RL01128-OP-0028)
        Includes document files in TXT and MS Word formats, audio files in WAV and AIFF formats, video files in Quicktime and MP4 formats, and still image files in JPEG and PNG formats.
      - Trabajando for an Education, by:Marin, Dulce and Splawinski, Lisa, 2011; 29 files; approximately 100 megabytes. (Box 113, Digital-materials RL01128-SET-0021, Optical-disc RL01128-OP-0029)
      - Katie's Community Health Project, by: Cox, Katie, 2011; 90 files; approximately 275 megabytes. (Box 113, Digital-materials RL01128-SET-0021, Optical-disc RL01128-OP-0030)
        Includes still image files in JPEG format, document files in MS Word and Powerpoint formats, and video files in MP4 and AVI formats.
      - Untitled, by: Lopez, Diego and Arzaluz, Luis, 2011 (Box 113)
      - Hecho a Mano, by: Foster, Colton and Arevalo, Joanna V., 2011; Approximately 200 files; 1 gigabyte. (Box 113, Digital-materials RL01128-SET-0021, Optical-disc RL01128-OP-0031, RL01128-OP-0032)
        Includes still image files in JPEG format, audio files in WAV format, video files in AVI format, and document files in MS Word and Powerpoint formats.
      - The Dream, by: Ramirez, Laura and Pulido, Rigoberto, 2011; 75 files; approximately 25 megabytes. (Box 113, Digital-materials RL01128-SET-0021, Optical-disc RL01128-OP-0033)
      - Untitled, by: Ospina, Natalia and Torres, Lubella, 2011; 47 files; approximately 1 gigabyte. (Box 113, Digital-materials RL01128-SET-0021, Optical-disc RL01128-OP-0034)
        Includes audio files in WAV format, still image files in PNG format, and document files in MS Word and PDF formats.
      - Untitled, by: Levine, Robyn and Valencia, Maritza, 2011; 56 files; approximately 125 megabytes. (Box 113, Digital-materials RL01128-SET-0021, Optical-disc RL01128-OP-0035)
        Includes audio files in MP3 format, still image files in JPEG and PNG formats, and document files in MS Word and Powerpoint formats.
      - Echando la mano: Labor with and for Family, by: Bissette, Abigal; Shrader, Katie Cox and Kumar, Nandini, 2011; Approximately 50 files; 650 megabytes. (Box 113, Digital-materials RL01128-SET-0021, Optical-disc RL01128-OP-0036, RL01128-OP-0037)
        Disk image derived from video disc, as well as still image files in JPEG Format, document files in MS Word format, and audio files in MP3 format.
    - Café 71, unknown author, undated (Box 113)
    - SAF End of Summer (EOS) Celebration, 2008, by Leanne Tory-Murphy (Box 51)
    - 2010 ITF, SSC and Theater Photos, 2 folders (Box 51)
    - W-10: Yo también me puedo..., picture book by a child, undated (Box 51)
    - Photos from Dale Bones' farm by student, undated (Box 51)
    - Seira Reyes, 7 folders (Box 51)
    - Seira Reyes, An Artist's Journey, by: Samantha C. Fernández and Lorena E. Magaña-Ortiz, 2002 (Box 94)
    - Seira Reyes: An Artist's Journey, by: Fernández and Magaña-Ortiz, 2002 (Box 136)
    - Miscellaneous protest photos, undated (Box 51)
    - Ni de Aquí, Ni de Allá (Not from Here/Not from There), Kreps Gallery at CDS (slides), undated (Box 51)
    - 110B (slides), undated (Box 51)
    - Unlabeled slides, artwork, undated (Box 51)
    - April's community organizing presentation at school, 1 of 1 (Box 51)
    - Pender County AIM, undated (Box 51)
    - Staff scrapbooks 1-8, undated, 8 folders (Box 51)
    - Miscellaneous media, undated (Box 51)
    - Subject photos, undated, 1-4 of 6 folders (Box 51)